<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shipr In Blog</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>/</link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 18:11:38 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 18:11:38 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Another post that I just posted</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;This is how this all will work. see if permanent link regenerates&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 15:23:21 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/08/14/custom-blog-what</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/08/14/custom-blog-what</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome to Jekyll!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Test You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-ruby&quot; data-lang=&quot;ruby&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;def&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;puts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Hi, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;#{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;name&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;si&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;end&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;n&quot;&gt;print_hi&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s1&quot;&gt;&#39;Tom&#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;c1&quot;&gt;#=&amp;gt; prints &#39;Hi, Tom&#39; to STDOUT.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the &lt;a href=&quot;http://jekyllrb.com/docs/home&quot;&gt;Jekyll docs&lt;/a&gt; for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll&quot;&gt;Jekyll’s GitHub repo&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions, you can ask them on &lt;a href=&quot;https://talk.jekyllrb.com/&quot;&gt;Jekyll Talk&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 14 Aug 2016 15:23:21 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/08/14/welcome-to-jekyll</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/08/14/welcome-to-jekyll</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Portable Grand Piano Keyboard</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;People who are interested in buying home digital piano and looking for the suitable place to purchase it with the best possible price, then Musicians-Friend is an ideal place for them. They offer a huge collection of musical instruments with related accessories, you can view the product details in their web site and choose your favorite brand at an affordable price. If you need Yamaha &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.musiciansfriend.com/home-digital-pianos/yamaha-ypg-535-88-key-portable-grand-piano-keyboard&quot;&gt;ypg-535&lt;/a&gt; 88-key portable grand piano keyboard, you can easily compare the feature like price, compatibility, amplifier, digital effect and much more at one place that make your selection easier.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 23:38:45 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/08/11/portable-grand-piano-keyboard/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/08/11/portable-grand-piano-keyboard/</guid>
        
        
        <category>General</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Give Presence Not Presents</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Throughout the year we have many gift-giving opportunities to show love to those around us. From Christmas to Birthdays, Valentines Day and more, our thoughts turn to finding the perfect gift. Before you shop and wrap remember that our loved ones need more of our presence than our presents! This type of gift giving uses more creativity, less of our money and more of our heart. Need some ideas on how you can give of your presence and not just store bought presents?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DINNER FOR 2&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of purchasing restaurant gift certificates for someone, invite them to dinner with you! Make sure they understand that you are picking up the tab as your gift to them, but the real gift will be the time you get to spend together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SHOPPING SPREE GIFTS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My mother simply hates shopping for me. She also hates shopping with me. Ok, she hates shopping period. But she knows how much I love it! That’s why it is such a wonderful gift to me when she takes me on a shopping spree for my birthday every year. If you had planned to buy a loved one something at the store, you can still give of your presence too. Invite your special someone to come pick it out with you. I still remember when I was younger, and a boyfriend took me shopping. He had me model the knit sweater for him before he bought it for me. The sweater is long gone and moth eaten but the memory is still knit tightly in my mind.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;COUPONS&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clipping coupons is an excellent way to save money when shopping but they are also a great way to save money when gift giving. The home computer has made coupon books easy and professional looking. Trying to think creatively about what your loved one needs is the hardest part of making meaningful coupons. Would your husband love his own indoor tailgate party with a coupon for a night of uninterrupted football coverage complete with his favorite snacks and drinks? Or maybe your young teenage daughter needs a coupon book offering taxi rides anywhere her and her friends want to be chauffeured for the night? You get the idea. Be creative.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;INCENTIVES &amp;amp; BRIBES&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever politically correct word you use, incentives for children to get good grades or allowance given to complete weekly chores or reach behavioral goals are generally money or present oriented. I would like to suggest that you substitute presence for presents in this situation too once in a while. My parents used to take me to a good movie when I got good grades at the end of each quarter, even if I would have preferred the cash like my friends got, it strengthened our relationship more than the money ever would have.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was potty training my oldest daughter, instead of giving her candy to reinforce her efforts, I would let her draw an activity from a jar. She knew that I would drop everything and give her my undivided attention and presence to read her a story, color with her, eat a Popsicle with her, etc. Now that this same daughter is 8 and she would much rather have me cater and entertain at her sleep over party, than to be given an allowance as appreciation for doing her chores!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you truly believe that Time = Money, than give a gift worth it’s wealth in gold.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2016 23:36:17 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/08/11/give-presence-not-presents/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/08/11/give-presence-not-presents/</guid>
        
        
        <category>General</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>June posts</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Test You’ll find this post in your &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;jekyll serve&lt;/code&gt;, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To add new posts, simply add a file in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;_posts&lt;/code&gt; directory that follows the convention &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;YYYY-MM-DD-name-of-post.ext&lt;/code&gt; and includes the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 15:23:21 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/07/14/old-post</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/07/14/old-post</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Japanese Brand Guitars</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As a guitarist, you want to buy a high-standard electric guitar that produced classic tone, then visit at MusiciansFriend. They offer a wide selection of leading brand &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.musiciansfriend.com/ibanez&quot;&gt;ibenez&lt;/a&gt; electric guitars at an affordable price. This is a Japanese brand and produces high quality acoustic, semi-acoustic guitars and bass guitars. The Ibenez products with descriptions are available in their web site, you can view all the products on one page that make your selection easier.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 May 2016 21:54:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/05/13/the-japanese-brand-guitars/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/05/13/the-japanese-brand-guitars/</guid>
        
        
        <category>General</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Manage Your Expectations on your quality of life!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;When I was a newbie in ‘the game of life,’ I wanted to succeed beyond my wildest dreams. I wanted to make it big and take on the world, all at once. My expectations were so high that not even Jack could reach them on his beanstalk. However, over time, after much frustration and burn out, I shifted to the other extreme by dropping my expectations, and dreams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea of lowering our expectations is a contradiction to the ‘parental voices’ that tells us that we should ‘reach for the stars,’ ‘raise our expectations,’ and ‘shoot for the moon.’ In theory, these are excellent ideals when chasing a dream. But, without some control, such ideals can burn you out, create frustration, and literally destroy your drive to attain any goals, lofty or otherwise. We’ve all either been there, or are there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you feel like you’ve run into a wall, or bumped your head on the ceiling, your expectations of what should be are probably forcing you to take ‘too big of a bite.’ But, don’t necessarily lower your expectations. Try managing your expectations to keep your dreams alive and continue your pursuit at a reasonable pace. Again, it seems like a contradiction to what we’ve all heard at one time or another. But, actually, there is a way to keep your ultimate goal in sight, while managing your expectations, so that you can keep your sanity and still achieve success in life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— Look at it! —-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Evel Knievel jumps canyons on various wonder-bikes, for fun! But, don’t think he just hopped on his bike one day and jumped over the Grand Canyon. Consider that he developed his skills over time to execute his lifetime of phenomenal jumps. But, if he had taken the jumps without building up to them, fear and inexperience would have destroyed the stunts. He had to start with small jumps to gain confidence until, eventually, he was able to make his jumps without hesitation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;High expectations can place you in a position of trying to jump your own canyons right out of the gate. Too many failed attempts can lead you to frustration and eventually, complete surrender of your goals. However, if such an attempt should succeed, it could land you in a situation that, while it looked good from a distance, might not be the place where you wanted to land.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— Break it down! —&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before you go too far on that jump across that canyon, make sure that you know exactly where you want to land. It is imperative that you define exactly what it is that you ultimately want in your life. Once you know what you want, break the process to reach this ‘vision’ down into reasonable steps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Instead of trying to jump the canyon immediately, try jumping a puddle to see if you can do it with confidence. Once you manage the puddle, take what you’ve learned, put it behind you, and go for something just outside of your comfort zone … perhaps a ditch. Such steps allow you to take on smaller pieces of the whole so that you can set reachable goals on the way to your vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— Changing directions! —&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only is this ‘stepping stone’ approach to attaining lofty goals and managing high expectations effective in moving you in the right direction, but you might also find that, the destination is something that you didn’t ‘expect.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the key—’did not expect.’ High expectations set on a vision that is ‘unknown’ can lead you sometimes place you further away from your vision then when you started. We see where we want to go, want so badly to get there, but have no idea what it takes or what it is that we’re pursuing. Even though the vision might be reasonable, it is the perception that we have of the vision that adds unnecessary stress to our daily lives in our pursuit of that vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we take small steps to reach our vision, we can adjust our path along the way. As we move toward and learn more of our ultimate destination, we might find that we don’t want the original vision. We learn that we might instead want the objective about 30 degrees off of our original. By moving along, one goal at a time, we are able to adjust to ensure that we land were we want to on the other side of our canyon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— Reapplying the expectations! —&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all develop a certain perspective of things based on the way that we’ve been raised, the experiences that we’ve encountered, and the successes or failures that we’ve had in our lives. Based on our perspective, we develop extraordinarily high expectations of things when we’re not sure of the results of our plight or goals in life. These expectations are built up to cover the doubts that we might have about the goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Realize that things are what they are, regardless of our perception. But, by accepting things as they are, and not what you would wish them to be, it makes it much easier to maneuver yourself in the direction you want to go. We must sometimes readjust our perspectives, our values and belief systems, to gain some control in our lives and obtain a clearer view of our paths.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— What’s next? —&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By taking on small pieces of the whole, we can easily adjust our path along the way. In this way, we must research our goals so that we can understand where we’re going. In breaking up the path into the smaller goals required to reach our vision, our expectations for our vision become clearer and less imperative. By managing our goals in this way, we automatically manage our expectations because we only have expectations of the immediate goal leading us in the direction of our ultimate vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Establish a new plan based on the individual components of your overall vision. Try moving forward with this new plan and see what happens. See how the newly managed goals and expectations work in your life and how you feel as you accomplish the smaller goals on the way to your vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not only will managing your expectations provide you with a more solid path to reach your vision, but it will also enhance your quality of life. Instead of being stressed, frustrated, and disappointed, you can now feel good about your forward momentum in your own life because you will know where you’re going and be able to handle the journey.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 May 2016 22:05:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/05/10/manage-your-expectations-on-your-quality-of-life/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/05/10/manage-your-expectations-on-your-quality-of-life/</guid>
        
        
        <category>General</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Quality Musical Instruments At Dallas</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;As a musician, you are searching for a right place nearby Dallas to buy an instrument with related accessories, then &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.guitarcenter.com&quot;&gt;guiatarcenter dallas&lt;/a&gt; is ideal for you. They are a leading retailer of musical instruments and related parts and offer them at a very reasonable price. The leading brands of products like guitars, drums, bass, mics and wireless, lighting and much more with the best quality, you can view their catalog compare the features at one place that make your selection easier.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 01:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/04/23/quality-musical-instruments-at-dallas/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/04/23/quality-musical-instruments-at-dallas/</guid>
        
        
        <category>General</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Ten Things That Successful Parents Do</title>
        <description>&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;They are leaders as well as parents. They don’t rely on the schools, the government, television, the movies or music to teach their children values and the difference between right and wrong. They do it themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;They have a vision for their family and its future, one that is discussed and shared often. And they support the vision with clearly articulated, clarified and communicated values and beliefs. Every action, behaviour, and decision is taken with those values and beliefs firmly in mind. They constantly emphasize the relationship between family successes and acting in accordance with the values and beliefs. They make a clear distinction between right and wrong. Everybody is clear on how things are to be done and why.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;They are behavioral models for their children. Their behaviors reflect those that they want the kids to emulate. They are honest because they value honesty; open because they value openness; forgiving because they value forgiveness. They make tough decisions when necessary and they take responsibility for the results. They don’t just tell their children what to value and believe; they show them through words and deeds.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;They enable their children. They communicate high, but achievable behavioral and performance expectations and provide the spiritual, emotional, physical, intellectual and financial resources the children need to successfully achieve them. They know that self-esteem is a function of achievement.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;They talk with their kids, not at them. They develop feedback loops so the children can come to understand the impact of their behaviour on others. They make sure the kids understand the relationship behaviour and consequences. And they distinguish between the child and his or her behaviour so, when there are problems, they unconditionally love the child while looking for a solution to the problem.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;They take pains to understand how children develop. As the children are finding their way in the world these parents use a combination of maturity and skill to firmly direct when direction is needed; discuss when the circumstances merit; push the kids away when they are ready to make provisional tries when they are ready to and, finally; they set them free altogether. Through it all, the door is left open for the kids to come back if they needed to.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;They take an active role in their children’s education, both formal and informal. They are active contributors to both the schools and communities. They enrich the home environment in every way they can. They go to concerts, games, on camping trips and, unfailingly, to the ceremonies that mark the graduations from one stage to the next.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Although their children are outstanding in any number of ways, these parents freely admit their kids were anything but perfect. They accept and openly talk about the fact that, while good kids, their children are just as prone as others to the vicissitudes of growing up and, on occasion, their behaviour reflects that fact.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;When the time comes, they discuss the future and provide appropriate advice and guidance regarding career and other life choices that children must eventually make.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Through it all they encourage independent, critical thinking so, in the final analysis, each child becomes his or her own person.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2016 00:50:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/04/23/ten-things-that-successful-parents-do/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/04/23/ten-things-that-successful-parents-do/</guid>
        
        
        <category>General</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Custom Printing Promotional Products</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;People who are looking for the promotional items to promote their business products, then visit at Print Globe. They offer diverse kind of products, business printing solutions, banners, flogs, signs and much more at an affordable price. Anyone is searching an inexpensive as well as effective product then, &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.printglobe.com/drinkware/can-coolers-koozies-and-drink-wraps/can-coolers-and-can-holders&quot;&gt;can koozies&lt;/a&gt; are ideal and make perfect promotion for any company. At PrintGlobe, you can find thousands of customizable bottle and can jackets to choose from them or create your own personalized koozies and upload them and get the same without any hassle.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beverage containers are designed to thermally insulate can holders, and available a wide range of colors and designs with multiple printing options, people can choose their custom printed can coolers with their company logo for their event or promotional purpose. Design your own exclusive custom koozies for your big event that everyone will love and really excited to make your promotional project as a successful and memorable one.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 20:59:00 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/2016/02/24/custom-printing-promotional-products/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/2016/02/24/custom-printing-promotional-products/</guid>
        
        
        <category>General</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
